I heard about this arduino project, and I saw it online -
私はこのarduinoのプロジェクトについて聞いて、私はそれをオンラインで見て-
- and I said 'Wow! a lot of people are starting to talk about this. I should check it out!'
- そして、私と同時期に、うわー！多くの人々がこの話を始めている。私はそれをチェックアウトする必要があります！
Because we wanted to make a tool for our students that was more modern than what was available on the market at that moment.
我々はよりその時点で、市場で入手可能であったものよりも現代だった我々の学生のためのツールを作りたいと思ってからです。
For me it was a case of - this is a tool that I could see using myself, and therefore I could believe in actually helping to get it out to a wider world.
これは、私は、自分自身を使用して見ることができたので、私は実際にはより広い世界にそれを取得するうえで信じることができたツールです-私にとっては、そうだった。
Open source hardware means to take back control of what is inside things.
オープンソースハードウェアは、物事の内側にあるものの制御を取り戻すことを意味します。
We wanted it to be open source - so everybody could come out, help, and contribute.
我々はオープンソースになることを望んでいた-ので、誰もが、助けて、出てくる可能性がと貢献しています。
For me, that's about giving people the information they need to recreate the piece of hardware for themselves.
私にとっては、そのことについて人々に自分自身のためのハードウェアの一部を再作成するために必要な情報を与えている。
I'm really passionate about arduino... because I really care about understanding more about how the world works.
私は本当にarduinoの情熱よ...私は本当にに関する詳細については、世界はどのように動作するか理解する気だ。
My advisors said that... there would come the day when there is more computers than people.
私のアドバイザーによると...人以上のコンピュータがあるときに日が来るだろう。
If every computer had a keyboard and mouse... and a screen, it would be impossible to command our lives.
すべてのコンピュータは、キーボードとマウスを持っていた場合は...と画面には、それが私たちの生活を指揮することは不可能です。
Then we started to figure out that there was a way to get a very nice ecosystem of people...
その後、我々は人々の非常に素晴らしい生態系を取得する方法があったことを把握し始めた...
...participating, and making extensions... making derivatives... and helping...
...参加し、拡張機能を作る...デリバティブを作る...と支援...
So it's kind of like I'm taking one step up a ladder. And then I'm helping other people go further up the ladder.
だから、私は梯子の上の一歩を取っているようなものだ。そして、私が手伝いをしている他の人が梯子の上、さらに進んでください。
So... we had to simplify the interface. And that's the beginning of a completely new way of looking at... computation.
だから... ...我々はインターフェイスを簡素化していた。そして、それは見ての全く新しい方法の始まりです...計算。
Arduino: The Documentary
アードウイーノ: ザ・ドキュメンタリー
The very first thing I tried to do with an arduino was run a 3D printer.
arduinoは3Dプリンタを実行されたと私が試した、非常に最初にすること。
...so I make moving cakes and singing cakes...
...ので、私はケーキと歌のケーキを移動する...
So we make puppets with the arduino...
そこで、arduinoので人形を作る...
One of my students is building a guitar.
私の生徒の一人はギターを構築しています。
Here's a... here's a robot...
これはロボットです。
If I tilt, you see the light goes left - if I go up...
私が傾けている場合は、光が左に行くを参照してください-私が行けば...
Many people have built helicopters with four or six motors.
多くの人々が4つまたは6つのモータとヘリコプター組み込まれています。
Suddenly a message arrived telling us that arduino...
突然のメッセージが私たちをことを伝える到着arduinoの...
And obviously I said OK... this is just too much.
そして、明らかに私はOKだ...これはあまりにも似ています。
It ended up being a 17 year old who made the satellite.
それが17年には、衛星を行ったユーザーを古いものになってしまいました。
Arduino: The Documentary
アードウイーノ: ザ・ドキュメンタリー
www.arduinothedocumentary.org
www.arduinothedocumentary.org